[
    {
        "title": "Genki Lesson 1 Grammar",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            { 
                "question": "XはYです。", 
                "answer": "X is Y.; As for X, it is Y." 
            }, 
            { 
                "question": "Mr. Yamashita is a teacher. | As for Mr. Yamashita, he is a teacher.", 
                "answer": "やましたさんは、せんせいです" 
            }, 
            { 
                "question": "(Are you) an international student?", 
                "answer": "りゅうがくせいですか" 
            }, 
            { 
                "question": "What is your major?", 
                "answer": "せんこうはなにですか" 
            }, 
            { 
                "question": "What year are you in college?", 
                "answer": "なんねんせいですか" 
            }, 
            { 
                "question": "a student of the Japanese language", 
                "answer": "にほんごのがくせい" 
            }, 
            { 
                "question": "a college professor", 
                "answer": "だいがくのせんせい" 
            }, 
            { 
                "question": "Is that so? | I see.", 
                "answer": "そうですか" 
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki Greetings",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "はじめまして。",
                "answer": "Nice to meet you."
            },
            {
                "question": "よろしくおねがいします。",
                "answer": "Please extend special favor for me."
            },
            {
                "question": "おはよう。",
                "answer": "Good morning (Casual)."
            },
            {
                "question": "おはようございます。",
                "answer": "Good morning (Polite)."
            },
            {
                "question": "こんにちは。",
                "answer": "Hello. / Good afternoon."
            },
            {
                "question": "こんばんは。",
                "answer": "Good evening."
            },
            {
                "question": "ごめんなさい。",
                "answer": "I am sorry."
            },
            {
                "question": "すみません。",
                "answer": "Excuse me / I am sorry."
            },
            {
                "question": "さようなら。",
                "answer": "Good bye."
            },
            {
                "question": "じゃ、また。",
                "answer": "See you later."
            },
            {
                "question": "おやすみなさい。",
                "answer": "Good night."
            },
            {
                "question": "しつれいします。",
                "answer": "Excuse me (for leaving earlier than you do.)"
            },
            {
                "question": "ありがとう。",
                "answer": "Thank you."
            },
            {
                "question": "ありがとうございます。",
                "answer": "Thank you very much."
            },
            {
                "question": "どういたしまして。",
                "answer": "You are welcome."
            },
            {
                "question": "いってらっしゃい。",
                "answer": "Have a nice day."
            },
            {
                "question": "いってきます。",
                "answer": "I am leaving."
            },
            {
                "question": "ただいま。",
                "answer": "I am home."
            },
            {
                "question": "おかえりなさい。",
                "answer": "Welcome back."
            },
            {
                "question": "いただきます。",
                "answer": "I will start eating."
            },
            {
                "question": "ごちそうさまでした。",
                "answer": "I have finished eating."
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki Lesson 1 Vocabulary",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あの",
                "answer": "um..."
            },
            {
                "question": "いま",
                "answer": "now"
            },
            {
                "question": "えいご",
                "answer": "English"
            },
            {
                "question": "ええ",
                "answer": "yes (informal)"
            },
            {
                "question": "がくせい",
                "answer": "student"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜ご",
                "answer": "〜language"
            },
            {
                "question": "こうこう",
                "answer": "high school"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごご",
                "answer": "PM"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごぜん",
                "answer": "AM"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜さい",
                "answer": "〜years old"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜さん",
                "answer": "Mr./Mrs.〜"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜じ",
                "answer": "〜o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜じん",
                "answer": "nationality; 〜person"
            },
            {
                "question": "せんこう",
                "answer": "major"
            },
            {
                "question": "せんせい",
                "answer": "teacher"
            },
            {
                "question": "そうです",
                "answer": "That's right"
            },
            {
                "question": "そうですか",
                "answer": "I see"
            },
            {
                "question": "だいがく",
                "answer": "university"
            },
            {
                "question": "でんわ",
                "answer": "telephone"
            },
            {
                "question": "ともだち",
                "answer": "friend"
            },
            {
                "question": "なまえ",
                "answer": "name"
            },
            {
                "question": "なに",
                "answer": "what"
            },
            {
                "question": "にほん",
                "answer": "Japan"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜ねんせい",
                "answer": "〜th year student"
            },
            {
                "question": "はい",
                "answer": "yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "はん",
                "answer": "half (an hour; :30)"
            },
            {
                "question": "ばんごう",
                "answer": "number"
            },
            {
                "question": "りゅうがくせい",
                "answer": "international student; exchange student"
            },
            {
                "question": "わたし",
                "answer": "I"
            },
            {
                "question": "アメリカ",
                "answer": "America"
            },
            {
                "question": "イギリス",
                "answer": "England"
            },
            {
                "question": "オーストラリア",
                "answer": "Australia"
            },
            {
                "question": "かんこく",
                "answer": "Korea"
            },
            {
                "question": "スウェーデン",
                "answer": "Sweden"
            },
            {
                "question": "ちゅうごく",
                "answer": "China"
            },
            {
                "question": "かがく",
                "answer": "science"
            },
            {
                "question": "けいざい",
                "answer": "economics"
            },
            {
                "question": "こくさいかんけい",
                "answer": "international relations"
            },
            {
                "question": "コンピューター",
                "answer": "computer"
            },
            {
                "question": "じんるいがく",
                "answer": "anthropology"
            },
            {
                "question": "せいじ",
                "answer": "politics"
            },
            {
                "question": "ビジネス",
                "answer": "business"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぶんがく",
                "answer": "literature"
            },
            {
                "question": "れきし",
                "answer": "history"
            },
            {
                "question": "しごと",
                "answer": "job"
            },
            {
                "question": "いしゃ",
                "answer": "doctor"
            },
            {
                "question": "かいしゃいん",
                "answer": "company worker"
            },
            {
                "question": "こうこうせい",
                "answer": "high school student"
            },
            {
                "question": "しゅふ",
                "answer": "housewife"
            },
            {
                "question": "だいがくいんせい",
                "answer": "graduate student"
            },
            {
                "question": "だいがくせい",
                "answer": "university student"
            },
            {
                "question": "べんごし",
                "answer": "lawyer"
            },
            {
                "question": "おかあさん",
                "answer": "mother"
            },
            {
                "question": "おとうさん",
                "answer": "father"
            },
            {
                "question": "おねえさん",
                "answer": "older sister"
            },
            {
                "question": "おにいさん",
                "answer": "older brother"
            },
            {
                "question": "いもうと",
                "answer": "younger sister"
            },
            {
                "question": "おとうと",
                "answer": "younger brother"
            },
            {
                "question": "なんさいですか。",
                "answer": "How old are you?"
            },
            {
                "question": "でんわぱんごうはなんですか。",
                "answer": "What is your telephone number?"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "さ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "し",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "す",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "せ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "そ",
                "answer": "so"
            },
            {
                "question": "た",
                "answer": "ta"
            },
            {
                "question": "ち",
                "answer": "chi"
            },
            {
                "question": "つ",
                "answer": "tsu"
            },
            {
                "question": "て",
                "answer": "te"
            },
            {
                "question": "と",
                "answer": "to"
            },
            {
                "question": "な",
                "answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "question": "に",
                "answer": "ni"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぬ",
                "answer": "nu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ね",
                "answer": "ne"
            },
            {
                "question": "の",
                "answer": "no"
            },
            {
                "question": "は",
                "answer": "ha"
            },
            {
                "question": "ひ",
                "answer": "hi"
            },
            {
                "question": "ふ",
                "answer": "fu"
            },
            {
                "question": "へ",
                "answer": "he"
            },
            {
                "question": "ほ",
                "answer": "ho"
            },
            {
                "question": "ま",
                "answer": "ma"
            },
            {
                "question": "み",
                "answer": "mi"
            },
            {
                "question": "む",
                "answer": "mu"
            },
            {
                "question": "め",
                "answer": "me"
            },
            {
                "question": "も",
                "answer": "mo"
            },
            {
                "question": "や",
                "answer": "ya"
            },
            {
                "question": "ゆ",
                "answer": "yu"
            },
            {
                "question": "よ",
                "answer": "yo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ら",
                "answer": "ra"
            },
            {
                "question": "り",
                "answer": "ri"
            },
            {
                "question": "る",
                "answer": "ru"
            },
            {
                "question": "れ",
                "answer": "re"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろ",
                "answer": "ro"
            },
            {
                "question": "わ",
                "answer": "wa"
            },
            {
                "question": "を",
                "answer": "wo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ん",
                "answer": "n"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki: Chapter 1: Numbers",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ゼロ・れい",
                "answer": "0"
            },
            {
                "question": "いち （一）",
                "answer": "1"
            },
            {
                "question": "に （二）",
                "answer": "2"
            },
            {
                "question": "さん （三）",
                "answer": "3"
            },
            {
                "question": "し・よん （四）",
                "answer": "4"
            },
            {
                "question": "ご （五）",
                "answer": "5"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろく （六）",
                "answer": "6"
            },
            {
                "question": "なな （七）",
                "answer": "7"
            },
            {
                "question": "はち （八）",
                "answer": "8"
            },
            {
                "question": "きゅう （九）",
                "answer": "9"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅう （十）",
                "answer": "10"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅういち （十一）",
                "answer": "11"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうに （十二）",
                "answer": "12"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうさん （十三）",
                "answer": "13"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうよん・じゅうし （十四）",
                "answer": "14"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうご （十五）",
                "answer": "15"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうろく （十六）",
                "answer": "16"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうなな （十七）",
                "answer": "17"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうはち （十八）",
                "answer": "18"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうきゅう （十九）",
                "answer": "19"
            },
            {
                "question": "にじゅう （二十）",
                "answer": "20"
            },
            {
                "question": "さんじゅう （三十）",
                "answer": "30"
            },
            {
                "question": "よんじゅう （四十）",
                "answer": "40"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごじゅう （五十）",
                "answer": "50"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろくじゅう （六十）",
                "answer": "60"
            },
            {
                "question": "ななじゅう （七十）",
                "answer": "70"
            },
            {
                "question": "はちじゅう （八十）",
                "answer": "80"
            },
            {
                "question": "きゅうじゅう （九十）",
                "answer": "90"
            },
            {
                "question": "ひゃく （百）",
                "answer": "100"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ぴゃ",
                "answer": "Pya"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぴょ",
                "answer": "Pyo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぴゅ",
                "answer": "Pyu"
            },
            {
                "question": "びゃ",
                "answer": "Bya"
            },
            {
                "question": "びょ",
                "answer": "Byo"
            },
            {
                "question": "びゅ",
                "answer": "Byu"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゃ",
                "answer": "Jya"
            },
            {
                "question": "じょ",
                "answer": "Jyo"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅ",
                "answer": "Jyu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぎゃ",
                "answer": "Gya"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぎょ",
                "answer": "Gyo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぎゅ",
                "answer": "Gyu"
            },
            {
                "question": "りゃ",
                "answer": "Rya"
            },
            {
                "question": "りょ",
                "answer": "Ryo"
            },
            {
                "question": "りゅ",
                "answer": "Ryu"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki Lesson 1 Vocabulary",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "えいご",
                "answer": "English language"
            },
            {
                "question": "がくせい",
                "answer": "student"
            },
            {
                "question": "にほんご",
                "answer": "Japanese language"
            },
            {
                "question": "こうこう",
                "answer": "high school"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごご",
                "answer": "pm"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごぜん",
                "answer": "am"
            },
            {
                "question": "さい",
                "answer": "years old"
            },
            {
                "question": "じ",
                "answer": "o' clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "いちじ",
                "answer": "one o' clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "じん",
                "answer": "person (add to country names to express nationality)"
            },
            {
                "question": "にほんじん",
                "answer": "Japanese person"
            },
            {
                "question": "せんせい",
                "answer": "teacher, master (of subject or profession)"
            },
            {
                "question": "だいがく",
                "answer": "college"
            },
            {
                "question": "でんわ",
                "answer": "phone"
            },
            {
                "question": "ともだち",
                "answer": "friend"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki 1: Time",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "いちじ",
                "answer": "One o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "にじ",
                "answer": "Two o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "さんじ",
                "answer": "Three o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "よじ",
                "answer": "Four o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごじ",
                "answer": "Five o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろくじ",
                "answer": "Six o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "しちじ",
                "answer": "Seven o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "はちじ",
                "answer": "Eight o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "くじ",
                "answer": "Nine o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうじ",
                "answer": "Ten o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅういちじ",
                "answer": "Eleven o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうにじ",
                "answer": "Twelve o'clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜はん",
                "answer": "Half past"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごぜん",
                "answer": "AM"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごご",
                "answer": "PM"
            },
            {
                "question": "いっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 1"
            },
            {
                "question": "にふん",
                "answer": "Minute 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "さんぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 3"
            },
            {
                "question": "よんぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 4"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごふん",
                "answer": "Minute 5"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 6"
            },
            {
                "question": "ななふん",
                "answer": "Minute 7"
            },
            {
                "question": "はっぷん・はちふん",
                "answer": "Minute 8"
            },
            {
                "question": "きゅうふん",
                "answer": "Minute 9"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうぷん/じっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 10"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅういっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 11"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうにふん",
                "answer": "Minute 12"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうさんぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 13"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうよんぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 14"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうごふん",
                "answer": "Minute 15"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうろっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 16"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうななふん",
                "answer": "Minute 17"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうはちふん・じゅうはっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 18"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゅうきゅうふん",
                "answer": "Minute 19"
            },
            {
                "question": "にじゅっぷん/にじっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 20"
            },
            {
                "question": "さんじゅっぷん/さんじっぷん",
                "answer": "Minute 30"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki L2 Vocabulary",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "これ",
                "answer": "this one"
            },
            {
                "question": "この",
                "answer": "this (+noun)"
            },
            {
                "question": "それ",
                "answer": "that one"
            },
            {
                "question": "その",
                "answer": "that [+noun]"
            },
            {
                "question": "あれ",
                "answer": "that one over there"
            },
            {
                "question": "あの",
                "answer": "that [+noun] overthere"
            },
            {
                "question": "どれ",
                "answer": "which one"
            },
            {
                "question": "どの",
                "answer": "which [+noun]"
            },
            {
                "question": "ここ",
                "answer": "here"
            },
            {
                "question": "そこ",
                "answer": "there"
            },
            {
                "question": "あそこ",
                "answer": "over there"
            },
            {
                "question": "どこ",
                "answer": "where"
            },
            {
                "question": "だれ",
                "answer": "who"
            },
            {
                "question": "おいしい",
                "answer": "delicious"
            },
            {
                "question": "さかな",
                "answer": "fish"
            },
            {
                "question": "とんかつ",
                "answer": "pork cutlet (name of a Japanese dish)"
            },
            {
                "question": "にく",
                "answer": "meat"
            },
            {
                "question": "メニュー",
                "answer": "menu"
            },
            {
                "question": "やさい",
                "answer": "vegetable"
            },
            {
                "question": "えんぴつ",
                "answer": "pencil"
            },
            {
                "question": "かさ",
                "answer": "umbrella"
            },
            {
                "question": "かばん",
                "answer": "bag"
            },
            {
                "question": "くつ",
                "answer": "shoes"
            },
            {
                "question": "さいふ",
                "answer": "wallet"
            },
            {
                "question": "ジーンズ",
                "answer": "jeans"
            },
            {
                "question": "じしょ",
                "answer": "dictionary"
            },
            {
                "question": "じてんしゃ",
                "answer": "bicycle"
            },
            {
                "question": "しんぶん",
                "answer": "newspaper"
            },
            {
                "question": "Tシャツ",
                "answer": "T-shirt"
            },
            {
                "question": "とけい",
                "answer": "watch; clock"
            },
            {
                "question": "ノート",
                "answer": "notebook"
            },
            {
                "question": "ペン",
                "answer": "pen"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぼうし",
                "answer": "hat; cap"
            },
            {
                "question": "ほん",
                "answer": "book"
            },
            {
                "question": "きっさてん",
                "answer": "cafe"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぎんこう",
                "answer": "bank"
            },
            {
                "question": "トイレ",
                "answer": "toilet; restroom"
            },
            {
                "question": "としょかん",
                "answer": "library"
            },
            {
                "question": "ゆうびんきょく",
                "answer": "post office"
            },
            {
                "question": "アメリカ",
                "answer": "U.S.A."
            },
            {
                "question": "イギリス",
                "answer": "Britain"
            },
            {
                "question": "かんこく",
                "answer": "Korea"
            },
            {
                "question": "ちゅうごく",
                "answer": "China"
            },
            {
                "question": "けいざい",
                "answer": "economics"
            },
            {
                "question": "コンピューター",
                "answer": "computer"
            },
            {
                "question": "ビジネス",
                "answer": "business"
            },
            {
                "question": "れきし",
                "answer": "history"
            },
            {
                "question": "おかあさん",
                "answer": "mother"
            },
            {
                "question": "おとうさん",
                "answer": "father"
            },
            {
                "question": "いくら",
                "answer": "how much"
            },
            {
                "question": "〜えん",
                "answer": "~ yen"
            },
            {
                "question": "たかい",
                "answer": "expensive; high"
            },
            {
                "question": "いらっしゃいませ",
                "answer": "Welcome (to our store)."
            },
            {
                "question": "おねがいします",
                "answer": "~, please."
            },
            {
                "question": "ください",
                "answer": "Please give me ~"
            },
            {
                "question": "じゃあ",
                "answer": "well then... ; if that is the case..."
            },
            {
                "question": "どうぞ",
                "answer": "Please.; Here it is."
            },
            {
                "question": "どうも",
                "answer": "Thanks. (casual)"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki: Chapter 2: Numbers",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ひゃく",
                "answer": "100"
            },
            {
                "question": "にひゃく",
                "answer": "200"
            },
            {
                "question": "さんびゃく",
                "answer": "300"
            },
            {
                "question": "よんひゃく",
                "answer": "400"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごひゃく",
                "answer": "500"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろっぴゃく",
                "answer": "600"
            },
            {
                "question": "ななひゃく",
                "answer": "700"
            },
            {
                "question": "はっぴゃく",
                "answer": "800"
            },
            {
                "question": "きゅうひゃく",
                "answer": "900"
            },
            {
                "question": "せん",
                "answer": "1000"
            },
            {
                "question": "にせん",
                "answer": "2000"
            },
            {
                "question": "さんぜん",
                "answer": "3000"
            },
            {
                "question": "よんせん",
                "answer": "4000"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごせん",
                "answer": "5000"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろくせん",
                "answer": "6000"
            },
            {
                "question": "ななせん",
                "answer": "7000"
            },
            {
                "question": "はっせん",
                "answer": "8000"
            },
            {
                "question": "きゅうせん",
                "answer": "9000"
            },
            {
                "question": "いちまん",
                "answer": "10,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "にまん",
                "answer": "20,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "さんまん",
                "answer": "30,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "よんまん",
                "answer": "40,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "ごまん",
                "answer": "50,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろくまん",
                "answer": "60,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "ななまん",
                "answer": "70,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "はちまん",
                "answer": "80,000"
            },
            {
                "question": "きゅうまん",
                "answer": "90,000"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki- Useful Expressions in the Classroom",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "わかりましたか",
                "answer": "Do you understand?"
            },
            {
                "question": "わかりました",
                "answer": "I understand./I understood."
            },
            {
                "question": "わかりません",
                "answer": "I don't understand/I don't know"
            },
            {
                "question": "ゆっくりいってください",
                "answer": "Please say it slowly"
            },
            {
                "question": "もういちどいってください",
                "answer": "Please say it again"
            },
            {
                "question": "ちょっとまってください",
                "answer": "Please wait"
            },
            {
                "question": "きいてください",
                "answer": "Please listen./Please ask."
            },
            {
                "question": "10ページをみてください",
                "answer": "Please look at page 10."
            },
            {
                "question": "こくばん",
                "answer": "blackboard"
            },
            {
                "question": "でんき",
                "answer": "electricity, light"
            },
            {
                "question": "カーテン",
                "answer": "curtain"
            },
            {
                "question": "ドア",
                "answer": "door"
            },
            {
                "question": "まど",
                "answer": "window"
            },
            {
                "question": "いす",
                "answer": "chair"
            },
            {
                "question": "かばん",
                "answer": "bag"
            },
            {
                "question": "つくえ (机)",
                "answer": "desk"
            },
            {
                "question": "けしゴム",
                "answer": "eraser"
            },
            {
                "question": "ペン",
                "answer": "pen"
            },
            {
                "question": "じしょ",
                "answer": "dictionary"
            },
            {
                "question": "ほん",
                "answer": "book"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Katakana",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ア",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "イ",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "ウ",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "エ",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "オ",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "カ",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "キ",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "ク",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "ケ",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "コ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "サ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "シ",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "ス",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "セ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "ソ",
                "answer": "so"
            },
            {
                "question": "タ",
                "answer": "ta"
            },
            {
                "question": "チ",
                "answer": "chi"
            },
            {
                "question": "ツ",
                "answer": "tsu"
            },
            {
                "question": "テ",
                "answer": "te"
            },
            {
                "question": "ト",
                "answer": "to"
            },
            {
                "question": "ナ",
                "answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "question": "ニ",
                "answer": "ni"
            },
            {
                "question": "ヌ",
                "answer": "nu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ネ",
                "answer": "ne"
            },
            {
                "question": "ノ",
                "answer": "no"
            },
            {
                "question": "ハ",
                "answer": "ha"
            },
            {
                "question": "ヒ",
                "answer": "hi"
            },
            {
                "question": "フ",
                "answer": "fu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ヘ",
                "answer": "he"
            },
            {
                "question": "ホ",
                "answer": "ho"
            },
            {
                "question": "マ",
                "answer": "ma"
            },
            {
                "question": "ミ",
                "answer": "mi"
            },
            {
                "question": "ム",
                "answer": "mu"
            },
            {
                "question": "メ",
                "answer": "me"
            },
            {
                "question": "モ",
                "answer": "mo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ヤ",
                "answer": "ya"
            },
            {
                "question": "ユ",
                "answer": "yu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ヨ",
                "answer": "yo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ラ",
                "answer": "ra"
            },
            {
                "question": "リ",
                "answer": "ri"
            },
            {
                "question": "ル",
                "answer": "ru"
            },
            {
                "question": "レ",
                "answer": "re"
            },
            {
                "question": "ロ",
                "answer": "ro"
            },
            {
                "question": "ワ",
                "answer": "wa"
            },
            {
                "question": "ヲ",
                "answer": "wo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ン",
                "answer": "n"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana A - So",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "さ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "し",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "す",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "せ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "そ",
                "answer": "so"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "HIRAGANA A-KO",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana A to HO",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "さ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "し",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "す",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "せ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "そ",
                "answer": "so"
            },
            {
                "question": "た",
                "answer": "ta"
            },
            {
                "question": "ち",
                "answer": "chi"
            },
            {
                "question": "つ",
                "answer": "tsu"
            },
            {
                "question": "て",
                "answer": "te"
            },
            {
                "question": "と",
                "answer": "to"
            },
            {
                "question": "な",
                "answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "question": "に",
                "answer": "ni"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぬ",
                "answer": "nu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ね",
                "answer": "ne"
            },
            {
                "question": "の",
                "answer": "no"
            },
            {
                "question": "は",
                "answer": "ha"
            },
            {
                "question": "ひ",
                "answer": "hi"
            },
            {
                "question": "ふ",
                "answer": "fu"
            },
            {
                "question": "へ",
                "answer": "he"
            },
            {
                "question": "ほ",
                "answer": "ho"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana (a-to)",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "さ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "し",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "す",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "せ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "そ",
                "answer": "so"
            },
            {
                "question": "た",
                "answer": "ta"
            },
            {
                "question": "ち",
                "answer": "chi"
            },
            {
                "question": "つ",
                "answer": "tsu"
            },
            {
                "question": "て",
                "answer": "te"
            },
            {
                "question": "と",
                "answer": "to"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana A to NO",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "さ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "し",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "す",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "せ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "そ",
                "answer": "so"
            },
            {
                "question": "た",
                "answer": "ta"
            },
            {
                "question": "ち",
                "answer": "chi"
            },
            {
                "question": "つ",
                "answer": "tsu"
            },
            {
                "question": "て",
                "answer": "te"
            },
            {
                "question": "と",
                "answer": "to"
            },
            {
                "question": "な",
                "answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "question": "に",
                "answer": "ni"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぬ",
                "answer": "nu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ね",
                "answer": "ne"
            },
            {
                "question": "の",
                "answer": "no"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana A to MO",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "さ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "し",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "す",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "せ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "そ",
                "answer": "so"
            },
            {
                "question": "た",
                "answer": "ta"
            },
            {
                "question": "ち",
                "answer": "chi"
            },
            {
                "question": "つ",
                "answer": "tsu"
            },
            {
                "question": "て",
                "answer": "te"
            },
            {
                "question": "と",
                "answer": "to"
            },
            {
                "question": "な",
                "answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "question": "に",
                "answer": "ni"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぬ",
                "answer": "nu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ね",
                "answer": "ne"
            },
            {
                "question": "の",
                "answer": "no"
            },
            {
                "question": "は",
                "answer": "ha"
            },
            {
                "question": "ひ",
                "answer": "hi"
            },
            {
                "question": "ふ",
                "answer": "fu"
            },
            {
                "question": "へ",
                "answer": "he"
            },
            {
                "question": "ほ",
                "answer": "ho"
            },
            {
                "question": "ま",
                "answer": "ma"
            },
            {
                "question": "み",
                "answer": "mi"
            },
            {
                "question": "む",
                "answer": "mu"
            },
            {
                "question": "め",
                "answer": "me"
            },
            {
                "question": "も",
                "answer": "mo"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Hiragana A to RO",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "あ",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "い",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "う",
                "answer": "u"
            },
            {
                "question": "え",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "お",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "か",
                "answer": "ka"
            },
            {
                "question": "き",
                "answer": "ki"
            },
            {
                "question": "く",
                "answer": "ku"
            },
            {
                "question": "け",
                "answer": "ke"
            },
            {
                "question": "こ",
                "answer": "ko"
            },
            {
                "question": "さ",
                "answer": "sa"
            },
            {
                "question": "し",
                "answer": "shi"
            },
            {
                "question": "す",
                "answer": "su"
            },
            {
                "question": "せ",
                "answer": "se"
            },
            {
                "question": "そ",
                "answer": "so"
            },
            {
                "question": "た",
                "answer": "ta"
            },
            {
                "question": "ち",
                "answer": "chi"
            },
            {
                "question": "つ",
                "answer": "tsu"
            },
            {
                "question": "て",
                "answer": "te"
            },
            {
                "question": "と",
                "answer": "to"
            },
            {
                "question": "な",
                "answer": "na"
            },
            {
                "question": "に",
                "answer": "ni"
            },
            {
                "question": "ぬ",
                "answer": "nu"
            },
            {
                "question": "ね",
                "answer": "ne"
            },
            {
                "question": "の",
                "answer": "no"
            },
            {
                "question": "は",
                "answer": "ha"
            },
            {
                "question": "ひ",
                "answer": "hi"
            },
            {
                "question": "ふ",
                "answer": "fu"
            },
            {
                "question": "へ",
                "answer": "he"
            },
            {
                "question": "ほ",
                "answer": "ho"
            },
            {
                "question": "ま",
                "answer": "ma"
            },
            {
                "question": "み",
                "answer": "mi"
            },
            {
                "question": "む",
                "answer": "mu"
            },
            {
                "question": "め",
                "answer": "me"
            },
            {
                "question": "も",
                "answer": "mo"
            },
            {
                "question": "や",
                "answer": "ya"
            },
            {
                "question": "ゆ",
                "answer": "yu"
            },
            {
                "question": "よ",
                "answer": "yo"
            },
            {
                "question": "ら",
                "answer": "ra"
            },
            {
                "question": "り",
                "answer": "ri"
            },
            {
                "question": "る",
                "answer": "ru"
            },
            {
                "question": "れ",
                "answer": "re"
            },
            {
                "question": "ろ",
                "answer": "ro"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Genki Lesson 1 Greeting",
        "swapQA": false,
        "swapable": true,
        "hirakata": true,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "ohayoo",
                "answer": "Good morning"
            },
            {
                "question": "ohayoo gozaimasu",
                "answer": "Good morning"
            },
            {
                "question": "konnichiwa",
                "answer": "Hello"
            },
            {
                "question": "konbanwa",
                "answer": "Good evening"
            },
            {
                "question": "sayoonara",
                "answer": "Goodbye"
            },
            {
                "question": "jaamata",
                "answer": "See you"
            },
            {
                "question": "oyasuminasai",
                "answer": "Good night"
            },
            {
                "question": "arigatoo",
                "answer": "Thanks"
            },
            {
                "question": "arigatoo gozaimasu",
                "answer": "Thank you"
            },
            {
                "question": "sumimasen",
                "answer": "I'm sorry"
            },
            {
                "question": "iie",
                "answer": "no"
            },
            {
                "question": "sumimasen",
                "answer": "excuse me"
            },
            {
                "question": "itadakimasu",
                "answer": "Thank you for the meal"
            },
            {
                "question": "gochisoosamadeshita",
                "answer": "Thank you for the meal"
            },
            {
                "question": "hajimemashite",
                "answer": "First time"
            },
            {
                "question": "yoroshiku onegaishimasu",
                "answer": "Nice to meet you"
            },
            {
                "question": "ittekimasu",
                "answer": "I'm leaving home"
            },
            {
                "question": "itterasshai",
                "answer": "See you when you get back"
            },
            {
                "question": "okaerinsai",
                "answer": "Welcome home"
            },
            {
                "question": "tadaima",
                "answer": "I'm back"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Katakana a-no",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "a",
                "answer": "ア"
            },
            {
                "question": "i",
                "answer": "イ"
            },
            {
                "question": "u",
                "answer": "ウ"
            },
            {
                "question": "e",
                "answer": "エ"
            },
            {
                "question": "o",
                "answer": "オ"
            },
            {
                "question": "ka",
                "answer": "カ"
            },
            {
                "question": "ki",
                "answer": "キ"
            },
            {
                "question": "ku",
                "answer": "ク"
            },
            {
                "question": "ke",
                "answer": "ケ"
            },
            {
                "question": "ko",
                "answer": "コ"
            },
            {
                "question": "sa",
                "answer": "サ"
            },
            {
                "question": "shi",
                "answer": "シ"
            },
            {
                "question": "su",
                "answer": "ス"
            },
            {
                "question": "se",
                "answer": "セ"
            },
            {
                "question": "so",
                "answer": "ソ"
            },
            {
                "question": "ta",
                "answer": "タ"
            },
            {
                "question": "chi",
                "answer": "チ"
            },
            {
                "question": "tsu",
                "answer": "ツ"
            },
            {
                "question": "te",
                "answer": "テ"
            },
            {
                "question": "to",
                "answer": "ト"
            },
            {
                "question": "na",
                "answer": "ナ"
            },
            {
                "question": "ni",
                "answer": "ニ"
            },
            {
                "question": "nu",
                "answer": "ヌ"
            },
            {
                "question": "ne",
                "answer": "ネ"
            },
            {
                "question": "no",
                "answer": "ノ"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "title": "Katakana",
        "swapQA": true,
        "swapable": false,
        "hirakata": false,
        "cards": [
            {
                "question": "A",
                "answer": "ア"
            },
            {
                "question": "I",
                "answer": "イ"
            },
            {
                "question": "U",
                "answer": "ウ"
            },
            {
                "question": "E",
                "answer": "エ"
            },
            {
                "question": "O",
                "answer": "オ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ka",
                "answer": "カ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ki",
                "answer": "キ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ku",
                "answer": "ク"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ke",
                "answer": "ケ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ko",
                "answer": "コ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Sa",
                "answer": "サ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Shi",
                "answer": "シ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Su",
                "answer": "ス"
            },
            {
                "question": "Se",
                "answer": "セ"
            },
            {
                "question": "So",
                "answer": "ソ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ta",
                "answer": "タ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Chi",
                "answer": "チ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Tsu",
                "answer": "ツ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Te",
                "answer": "テ"
            },
            {
                "question": "To",
                "answer": "ト"
            },
            {
                "question": "Na",
                "answer": "ナ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ni",
                "answer": "ニ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Nu",
                "answer": "ヌ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ne",
                "answer": "ネ"
            },
            {
                "question": "No",
                "answer": "ノ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ha",
                "answer": "ハ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Hi",
                "answer": "ヒ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Fu/Hu",
                "answer": "フ"
            },
            {
                "question": "He",
                "answer": "ヘ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ho",
                "answer": "ホ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ma",
                "answer": "マ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Mi",
                "answer": "ミ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Mu",
                "answer": "ム"
            },
            {
                "question": "Me",
                "answer": "メ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Mo",
                "answer": "モ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ya",
                "answer": "ヤ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Yu",
                "answer": "ユ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Yo",
                "answer": "ヨ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ra",
                "answer": "ラ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ri",
                "answer": "リ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ru",
                "answer": "ル"
            },
            {
                "question": "Re",
                "answer": "レ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Ro",
                "answer": "ロ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Wa",
                "answer": "ワ"
            },
            {
                "question": "Wo",
                "answer": "ヲ"
            },
            {
                "question": "N",
                "answer": "ン"
            }
        ]
    }
]